<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Looking at Numbers</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Looking at Numbers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Light It Red: Exploring Bell Tower Celebrations with R</title>
      <link>/post/exploring-bell-tower-celebrations-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/exploring-bell-tower-celebrations-r/</guid>
      <description>NC State Belltower Among the sights to see when taking a trip to Raleigh is NC State’s iconic Belltower. Erected as a monument to honor fallen soldiers of WW1, the memorial Belltower has become a symbol of pride for NC State students and alumni.
On any given night, the bell tower might have a red illumination. Red bell tower lightings signify special achievements made by NC State organizations and staff as well as memorial holidays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing US Research and Development Spending for Tidy Tuesday and SWD Challenge</title>
      <link>/post/analyzing-us-agency-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/analyzing-us-agency-research/</guid>
      <description>I’m attempting to kill two birds (or two twitter hashtags) with one stone here. This is my first attempt at analyzing a weekly #tidytuesday data set; additonally, it’s my first go at the the monthly #swdchallenge. #TidyTuesday The data for week 7 of Tidy Tuesday is a group of datasets that detail US federal research and development spending by agency.
## [1] &amp;quot;department&amp;quot; &amp;quot;year&amp;quot; &amp;quot;rd_budget&amp;quot; ## [4] &amp;quot;total_outlays&amp;quot; &amp;quot;discretionary_outlays&amp;quot; &amp;quot;gdp&amp;quot; With there only being a a handful of features of the dataset, I thought first to see how R&amp;amp;D spending changed throughout time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Author-level blog performance from Google Analytics</title>
      <link>/post/wow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/wow/</guid>
      <description>Blogging has become common practice among businesses looking to connect with their customers. Behind every blogging operation though is a team of authors full of industry knowhow. Giving writers a way to track their performance can compel them to write better and more often. Using R and Google Analytics, I was able to aggregate blog traffic for my coworkers. Google Analytics is a commonly used tool for tracking site usage, and the googleAnalyticsR package is a great API wrapper for getting its data into R.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>